<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Juan Rodriguez Monti Blog</title>
    <link>https://juanrodriguezmonti.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Juan Rodriguez Monti Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>2016 - 2022 - Copyright Juan Rodriguez Monti All Rights Reserved</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 16 Jan 2022 19:12:26 -0300</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://juanrodriguezmonti.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Art_creation_with_python</title>
      <link>https://juanrodriguezmonti.github.io/post/art_creation_with_python/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jan 2022 19:12:26 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://juanrodriguezmonti.github.io/post/art_creation_with_python/</guid>
      <description>Art creation with Python, Machine Learning and Language Processing During the time that I spent on the weekend reading about new things and stuff that I consider awesome, I dive into an interesting and emerging field of AI which is Images and Art Creation.
To be more specific, I started to work with models that create images, pixel art, and art, and I found it incredible.
Some work performed here is related to upcoming academic works, so this is half for fun and half academic related stuff.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Big O Algorithm Complexity Cheatsheet for common data structures</title>
      <link>https://juanrodriguezmonti.github.io/post/bigocheatsheet/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jul 2018 20:05:11 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://juanrodriguezmonti.github.io/post/bigocheatsheet/</guid>
      <description>Big O Cheatsheet Complexity Efficiency of stacks, queues, linked lists, doubly linked lists, and more data structures when inserting, deleting and searching Big O notation is defined by Wikipedia as a mathematical notation that describes the limiting behavior of a function when the argument tends towards a particular value or infinity. It is a member of a family of notations invented by Paul Bachmann,[1] Edmund Landau,[2] and others, collectively called Bachmann–Landau notation or asymptotic notation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Automatic deploy method for your site made with Hugo content generator</title>
      <link>https://juanrodriguezmonti.github.io/post/deployhugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jul 2018 19:18:34 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://juanrodriguezmonti.github.io/post/deployhugo/</guid>
      <description>I use since some years Hugo as my static site generator. I like it a lot, it is fast, reliable, open source, with an amazing community and works perfectly well.
After you setup the site, you just create content, make the new content and upload it to your server.
You make the content available to the site with hugo , you serve the content to test it locally with hugo server, then you need to deploy the site.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Newblogagain</title>
      <link>https://juanrodriguezmonti.github.io/post/newblogagain/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jul 2018 16:59:00 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://juanrodriguezmonti.github.io/post/newblogagain/</guid>
      <description>Once again I&amp;rsquo;m making a new blog. The previous &amp;lsquo;New blog&amp;rsquo; blog was about two years ago.
In the middle many adventures, ideas, books, conferences, code, gadgets and other stuff of my interest happened.
Now, new blog, using the same static generator written in Go as before, to create it ( Hugo ), with new theme and some ideas.
I hope in this brand new &amp;lsquo;New blog&amp;rsquo; I could reach what I would like to complete now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About me!</title>
      <link>https://juanrodriguezmonti.github.io/page/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jul 2018 16:57:05 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://juanrodriguezmonti.github.io/page/about/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m Juan Rodríguez Monti. I&amp;rsquo;m from Argentina. I&amp;rsquo;m a programmer.
I like, in no specific order, Algorithms, Python, Data Structures, Maths, Machine Learning, Music, Philosophy, Books, Fútbol.
Feel free to contact me for new jobs, conferences, or (whatever-reason) you want.
You can reach me at rmontijuan &amp;lsquo;@&amp;rsquo; gmail &amp;lsquo;.&amp;rsquo; com !</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>my talks</title>
      <link>https://juanrodriguezmonti.github.io/page/talks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jul 2018 16:57:05 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://juanrodriguezmonti.github.io/page/talks/</guid>
      <description>Some of my latest talks  Introduccion a PyQt - PyConEs 2015 - Almeria - Universidad de Almeria Eventos Python usando Python - PyConEs 2015 - Almeria - Universidad de Almeria Introduccion al framework web Django - 2009 - FLISOL PERGAMINO - UNNOBA Software Libre en la empresa - 2008 - FLISOL PERGAMINO - UNNOBA  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Things to know before you start programming</title>
      <link>https://juanrodriguezmonti.github.io/post/thingstoknowbeforeyoustartprogramming/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2016 15:51:10 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://juanrodriguezmonti.github.io/post/thingstoknowbeforeyoustartprogramming/</guid>
      <description>Some days ago, I was reading Guido Van Rossum&amp;rsquo;s Google Plus Page, and I found a link that he shared under this description &amp;ldquo;I was so impressed with this I am posting it to G+ and tweeting it &amp;ldquo;. As I admire a lot this guy, because he is the creator of the greatest programming language ever existed, I inmediately opened it. The story is about the things and warnings you should know before you start programming, under the title; Things I Wish Someone Had Told Me When I Was Learning How to Code.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New blog</title>
      <link>https://juanrodriguezmonti.github.io/post/newblog/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2016 15:51:07 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://juanrodriguezmonti.github.io/post/newblog/</guid>
      <description>This is my new blog. Im gonna put here some stuff that I&amp;rsquo;ve written some time ago, and - hopefully - Im gonna complete it with brand new stuff, too.
Thanks!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://juanrodriguezmonti.github.io/md/art-creation-with-python-machine-learning-and-lan-c4b19aaa31f44f338e3f39bb2cb25c99/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://juanrodriguezmonti.github.io/md/art-creation-with-python-machine-learning-and-lan-c4b19aaa31f44f338e3f39bb2cb25c99/</guid>
      <description>Art creation with Python, Machine Learning and Language Processing During the time that I spent on the weekend reading about new things and stuff that I consider awesome, I dive into an interesting and emerging field of AI which is Images and Art Creation.
To be more specific, I started to work with models that create images, pixel art, and art, and I found it incredible.
Some work performed here is related to upcoming academic works, so this is half for fun and half academic related stuff.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
